{
    "1": {
        "question": "Which AWS networking service enables a company to create a virtual network within AWS?",
        "options": {
            "A": "AWS Config",
            "B": "Amazon Route 53",
            "C": "AWS Direct Connect",
            "D": "Amazon VPC"
        },
        "answer": "D"
    },
    "2": {
        "question": "With Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC), what is the maximum size IP address range you can have in a VPC?",
        "options": {
            "A": "A./28",
            "B": "B./16",
            "C": "C./30",
            "D": "D./24"
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    "3": {
        "question": "You need to allow resources in a private subnet to access the internet. Which of the following must be present to enable this access?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Network access control lists",
            "B": "Security groups",
            "C": "NAT gateway",
            "D": "Route tables"
        },
        "answer": "C"
    },
    "4": {
        "question": "Private subnets have direct access to the internet.",
        "answer": "F"
    },
    "5": {
        "question": "Which component of AWS Global Infrastructure does Amazon CloudFront use to ensure low-latency deliver?",
        "options": {
            "A": "AWS Regions",
            "B": "AWS Availability Zones",
            "C": "AWS edge locations",
            "D": "Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC)"
        },
        "answer": "C"
    },
    "6": {
        "question": "Which of the following is an optional security control that can be applied at the subnet layer of a VPC?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Network ACL",
            "B": "Security group",
            "C": "Web application firewall",
            "D": "Firewall"
        },
        "answer": "A"
    },
    "7": {
        "question": "What happens when you use Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) to create a new VPC?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Three subnets are created by default in one Availability Zone",
            "B": "A main route table is created by default",
            "C": "Three subnets are created by default- one for each Availability Zone",
            "D": "An internet gateway is created by default."
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    "8": {
        "question": "Which of the following can be used to protect Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) instances hosted in AWS?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Internet Gateway",
            "B": "All of the above",
            "C": "AMI",
            "D": "Security group"
        },
        "answer": "D"
    },
    "9": {
        "question": "You are a solutions architect who works at a large retail company that is migrating its existing infrastructure to AWS. You recommend that they use a custom VPC. When you create a VPC, you assign it to an IPv4 Classless Inter-Domain Routing (CIDR) block of 10.0.1.0/24 (which has 256 total IP addresses). How many IP addresses are available?",
        "options": {
            "A": "251",
            "B": "256",
            "C": "246",
            "D": "250"
        },
        "answer": "A"
    },
    "10": {
        "question": "With Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC), what is the smallest size subnet you can have in a VPC?",
        "options": {
            "A": "/28",
            "B": "/30",
            "C": "/24",
            "D": "/16"
        },
        "answer": "A"
    }
}